

M ABDUSH SHIDQI MUBARROK

087770925360 | shidqimubarrok17@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdush-shidqi-8871081b8/ | https://desty.page/diqdesign

Tawangrejo RT02 RW03 Wonodadi Blitar

Hi my name is Abdush Shidqi or you can call me Diqi. I am a graduate of the Department of Informatics Engineering at the Malang State Polytechnic in 2022. I really like things related to design. I have been active in design since 2018. I started by making posters, banners, branding, and others. However, since 2021 I started to focus on developing a career in UI/UX design until now. And now you can contact me for cooperation. Let's do it!!

Education Level

Malang State Polytechnic - Malang

Aug 2019 - Jul 2022

Diploma in Information Tehcnology, 3.20/4.00

. In this campus I am active in organizing and following many communities so that I have a lot of knowledge and experience

MAN 2 Tulungagung - Tulungagung

Aug 2016 - Jul 2019

High School Diploma in IPA, 8.60/10.00

. In this campus I am active in organizing and following many communities so that I have a lot of knowledge and experience

Work Experiences

Rohis Polinema - Malang Aug 2019 - Jul 2021

Designer

An Islamic organization located on the Malang State Polytechnic campus

- · I design posters, banners, event logos, and ppt designs
- · Here I not only learn about design but also manage time and team

Alterra Academy - Malang Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

UI/UX Design Internship

Alterra Academy is a digital transformation platform for all Indonesians to become the best quality Digital Talents in the Industry today

• I'm here to make various types of UI/UX designs. I work by using the design thinking method. In it there are stages of empathize, define, ideate, prototype, and test. Here I not only learn about design but also manage time and team. Until finally, in my last project, I worked on an application, namely vaccine booking apps. A vaccine ordering application that connects health facilities with candidates to be vaccinated. This application is made for web app and mobile app

Organisational Experience

Ikamanda Campus Fair 2021 - Tulungagung

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Head of Event

• I am here as the chief executive in charge of commanding the success of activities and managing the team to achieve goals

Patria Developer - Blitar Jun 2021 - Present

Designer

· I work on making designs such as event posters, event logos, and social media designs

Rohis Polinema - Malang Aug 2019 - Jul 2021

Head Of Design

- · I design posters, banners, event logos, and ppt designs.
- Here I'm not Only learn about design but also manage time and team.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- · Webinars Attended (2021): Grow With Google: Berinteraksi Secara Efektif Dengan Pelanggan Anda Melalui Konten Marketing
- Hard Skills (2022): Certificate MSIB Kampus Merdeka at Alterra Academy Batch 02: UI/UX Design
- · Hard Skills (2022): BWA Course : Mastering Figma A to Z Ecommerce UI Animation Design
- Webinars Attended (2020): Inixindo : Problem Solving with Digital
- Webinars Attended (2020): Inixindo : Digital Content Creator
- Hard Skills @ (2022): Bootcamp BWA UI/UX Designer with Figma (E Wallet App)